<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources on We use computers to combat climate change.</title><link>/resource/</link><description>Recent content in Resources on We use computers to combat climate change.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/resource/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apps</title><link>/resource/apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resource/apps/</guid><description>Addressing climate change, one innovative application at a time.
Extreme Weather Prediction Weather prediction app for Singapore, using ConvLSTM models.
The Extreme Weather Prediction web app is capable of predicting daily precipitation of our area of study from 2015 to 2020. While using the web app, the user can select their timestep of interest and compare the predicted results with the WRF simulated data, which serves as our “true” data for comparison.</description></item><item><title>Data</title><link>/resource/data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resource/data/</guid><description>Highly-precise climate simulation with multi-scale and resolution.
Methodology The dataset is simulated using WRF4.3 by ERA5 (3 domains) and GCM (4 domains) forcing in NSCC HPC, as shown below.
Output files are in daily netCDF format with equal area projection at three domains (12.5km: Southeast Asia; 2.5km: Southern Malay Peninsula; 500m: Singapore).
Variables include temperature, precipitation, wind speed, relative humidity, and solar radiation.
Each daily file has eight timesteps (0, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18, 21; or 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18, 21, 0).</description></item><item><title>Tools</title><link>/resource/tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resource/tools/</guid><description>Contents comming soon!</description></item><item><title>Tutorials</title><link>/resource/tutorials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resource/tutorials/</guid><description>Jupyter Notebook for climate-related data analytics and visualization.
Access the GitHub repository for Python Climate Visuals.</description></item></channel></rss>